<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Safari Go]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Safari Go]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:59:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>PH: 0410 845 544</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/ph-0410-845-544/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">74949d75-5ecf-4dea-a4b5-f9add0db9ff1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:59:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>E:info@partysafari.com.au</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/einfopartysafaricomau/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ef91192e-07be-4389-8292-81451da07f39</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:58:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p> The children were from many different cultural backgrounds, including Rwanda, Fiji, Bosnia, Lebanon and Iraqi, and varied in age from toddler to 12. Simeon and his team were able to engage with the children on an individual level and encourage them to participate as a team. Which was no easy task when the kids ranged from extroverted stars of tomorrow to the more shy and reclusive.” Dijana Mackic Coordinator - BHHP Migrant Resource Centre</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/the-children-were-from-many-different-cultural-backgrounds/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b4722510-371f-4cd4-946d-471f702bbe11</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:57:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Party Safari hosted the Amazing Race at UTS Jumbunna in 2014 for a group of regional Indigenous students who came on campus for a University experience. Needless to say the students, their teachers and our staff had an extraordinary experience that will certainly last a life time. The activity was an excellent and fun way fro students to get to know the campus and UTS.The service was excellent from start to finish. Simeon and his team paid a lot of attention to detail which is very important. They tasks were very safe and fun at the same time. I would highly recommend Party Safari for large scale and complex events. Brigette Sancho Advancement Manager - University of Technology Sydney</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/the-party-safari-hosted-the-amazing-race-at-uts-jumbunna-in/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2f305664-1ea6-4f74-9c8d-3144c5a9c337</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>https://youtu.be/lGbPlTWK0H4</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/httpsyoutubelgbpltwk0h4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d0ac0332-45a0-4d28-acbf-7b9e8e67d305</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>YOUTH WORKSHOPS & EVENTS</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/youth-workshops-and-events/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1325baaf-b35d-48c7-bbef-dde68e9b5e61</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:52:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We here at SafariGo take great pride in being the supreme specialists when it comes to organising Youth Workshops and Events. We firmly believe the youth of today hold the key to unlock a better and brighter future for our planet, and our motto CREATE – INSPIRE – EDUCATE is the driving force behind the programs we design. SafariGo produces innovative Youth events for the 12-16 year old bracket, clocking into contemporary culture to engage and motivate acute, brilliant young minds. The best way to nurture life skills, growth and development is to disguise the lessons in a giant package of fun, and SafariGo are masters of that!Some of our past projects have included Youth Week activities and events, Multicultural Youth festivals, Music DJ and Dance workshops, and Art/Graffiti sessions. Our clients range from liaising with local councils, to charity and not-for-profit organisations, to school groups, and private companies, and the feedback is consistently amazing. In fact, check out the video below and see for yourself! SafariGO gives personalised service from the first seeds of conception, helping to guide your vision (and offering heaps of creative input!) right through the process, organising the mass preparation, and culminating in facilitating the actual workshop or event. We aim to connect by inspiring the mind and setting alight the spirit of Youth, and the results have been nothing short of astounding.Our team would love to be involved in making your next Youth Workshop or Event a roaring success. Whatever the task, whatever the budget, SafariGo will tackle any challenge and produce an experience with memories that live on long after the actual date.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/youth-workshops-and-events-we-here-at-safarigo-take-great-prid/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">664d9346-bfdc-4e31-b50f-07f7bb168399</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cc8e1499-14bd-4eda-9b3e-5f6029169911.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/42c48a36-d44e-4573-a32c-dd7edbc49868/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">42c48a36-d44e-4573-a32c-dd7edbc49868</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 07:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY EVENTS]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>PHOTOGRAPHY EVENTS</h1><p> Fancy yourself a bit of a photographer? Think you have an eye for what looks great on camera? Itching to get shooting but not quite sure how to get started in the commercial world? SafariEye could have just what you’re after! Our photography workshops provide the set, the lighting, the models, the product, and all you have to do is turn up with your camera and shoot! You can literally walk into a mock-commercial scenario where YOU are in charge of photography. Imagination abounds – perhaps a roaring 20’s Great Gatsby theme, or an exotic tropical island shoot, or maybe something more adventurous like letting us bring the wild heart of Africa to you!You bring your camera and materials, and we do the rest. It’s that easy. Our workshops also invite an industry professional guest - it may be a stylist to share some handy tips, or might be a director or industry photographer to pass on their knowledge – each workshop is different. SafariEye caters for beginners through to the more accomplished photographer, basically anyone with a passion for taking pictures!Come and experiment with your creativity, make a mock-ad, meet new people and network, challenge yourself, learn, laugh, get inspired, explore new ideas in a supportive environment - all whilst having HEAPS of fun! For more information and check out what workshops are currently on offer. CONTACT US TODAY </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2988b945-a593-4c90-bb22-2632f0fc819c.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-go/photography-events/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">931df178-d683-43fb-9469-417d6a609500</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 13:11:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>